storageo.com 2013-12-26

# Storageo | Privacy Policy

## Storageo Privacy Policy

The privacy and security of your personal information is our top priority.

At Storageo, we believe it is important to protect the privacy of our customers, as well as the privacy of visitors to our web site. We know that you care about how your personal information is collected, updated, used and shared, and we want to help you make knowledgeable choices about the information you provide to us.  
This Privacy and Security Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) explains and summarizes how we collect, use and protect your personal information as you interact with us directly, by phone, online and through our customer support services. This Privacy Policy applies to Storageo’s operations in the United States and to its web site located at www.Storageo.com.   
By using our services and/or our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Storageo consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable privacy and data protection laws.

**Our Privacy Policy will Change Over Time**  
Our Privacy Policy may change over time as we seek to improve the services we provide. We will post the revised Privacy Policy on our web site. We encourage you to refer to the Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current practices. If you are an existing customer of Storageo, we will attempt to notify you of material changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued access and use of www.Storageo.com and Storageo’s services constitutes your acceptance of any changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Types of Information Storageo Collects About You**  
Storageo collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from the use of our web site. We receive and store information you enter on www.Storageo.com or give to us in any other way. For example, you may provide information to us when you make a reservation for our storage services, enter into a lease/rental agreement with us, use our site to send your boxes to our warehouse for storage, use automatic bill pay or go online to make a payment on your account, make a customer service request or inquiry, or apply for a job with us. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information. We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit our site. We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in communicating with you regarding special offers that we think will be of interest to you, and we may add that information to the information we collected about you.

**How We Use Information About You**  
We use information we have collected about you to provide you with our storage and other services, to respond to customer inquiries and complaints, to maintain and collect payment on your account with us, to enforce your agreements with us, and to provide you with marketing and promotional information about products and services we believe are of interest to you.   
 **We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason.  
We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so. **  
We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, to protect against fraud or security hazards. 

**Our Security Practices**  
Our internal data security policies restrict access to customers’ personal information to authorized employees, agents and subcontractors with a “need to know,” and we train such persons on the protection of your information. These persons may use our customers’ personal information for Storageo business purposes only. Our employees are bound by our policies to maintain the confidentiality of our customers’ personal information. Employees who violate their confidentiality obligations are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers’ personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to Storageo.com, we make use of secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Personal information is maintained within a secure Windows NT Server environment. We also use encryption techniques and authentication procedures. ****

**What Else Should I Know About My Privacy?**  
You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your user id and password and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity, both online and off-line.
